<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Dunst</title>
    <link>https://dunst-project.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Dunst</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://dunst-project.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Showcase</title>
      <link>https://dunst-project.org/showcase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dunst-project.org/showcase/</guid>
      <description>We are searching for new screenshots to showcase Dunst&amp;rsquo;s features. It would be great if they used new features, such as color gradients (highlight can receive a list of colors) or custom rounded corners (corners, progress_bar_corners and icon_corners).&#xA;To learn more and share your riced configuration see #826.&#xA;Updated config file here</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Download</title>
      <link>https://dunst-project.org/download/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dunst-project.org/download/</guid>
      <description>The current stable version of Dunst is 1.12.0 released on November 30 2024.&#xA;Source tarball Code repository (Github) Release Notes For v1.12.0 There have been many important contributions in the last few months. Some notable changes are: adding hot-reload for the configuration, exporting rules via dunstctl, adding color gradients, removing default hard-coded icons. For detailed information consult the changelog.&#xA;Important notice for all users:&#xA;The behaviour of the setting height has been changed in a breaking way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Documentation</title>
      <link>https://dunst-project.org/documentation/dependencies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dunst-project.org/documentation/dependencies/</guid>
      <description>Dunst requires these libraries to compile.&#xA;gio-2.0 gdk-pixbuf-2.0 glib-2.0 pangocairo libnotify (optional, for dunstify) wayland-client (optional, for wayland) wayland-cursor (optional, for wayland) x11 (optional, for xorg) xinerama (optional, for xorg) xext (optional, for xorg) xrandr (optional, for xorg) xscrnsaver (optional, for xorg) Additionally, gdk-pixbuf has librsvg as an optional runtime dependency (for loading svg files).&#xA;NOTE: dunstctl uses the busctl for displaying rules and history. This command is usually provided by systemd.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Documentation</title>
      <link>https://dunst-project.org/documentation/dunstctl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dunst-project.org/documentation/dunstctl/</guid>
      <description>&lt;?xml version=&#34;1.0&#34; ?&gt; &lt;!DOCTYPE html PUBLIC &#34;-//W3C//DTD XHTML 1.0 Strict//EN&#34; &#34;http://www.w3.org/TR/xhtml1/DTD/xhtml1-strict.dtd&#34;&gt; dunstctl - Command line control utility for dunst, a customizable and lightweight notification-daemon NAME SYNOPSIS COMMANDS NAME dunstctl - Command line control utility for dunst, a customizable and lightweight notification-daemon&#xA;SYNOPSIS dunstctl COMMAND [PARAMETER]&#xA;COMMANDS action notification_position Performs the default action or, if not available, opens the context menu of the notification at the given position (starting count at the top, first notification being 0).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Documentation</title>
      <link>https://dunst-project.org/documentation/dunst/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dunst-project.org/documentation/dunst/</guid>
      <description>&lt;?xml version=&#34;1.0&#34; ?&gt; &lt;!DOCTYPE html PUBLIC &#34;-//W3C//DTD XHTML 1.0 Strict//EN&#34; &#34;http://www.w3.org/TR/xhtml1/DTD/xhtml1-strict.dtd&#34;&gt; dunst - A customizable and lightweight notification-daemon NAME SYNOPSIS DESCRIPTION Autostarting dunst COMMAND LINE OPTIONS CONFIGURATION NOTIFY-SEND MISCELLANEOUS FILES AUTHORS REPORTING BUGS COPYRIGHT SEE ALSO NAME dunst - A customizable and lightweight notification-daemon&#xA;SYNOPSIS dunst [-conf file] [-verbosity v] [-print] [--startup_notification]&#xA;DESCRIPTION Dunst is a highly configurable and lightweight notification daemon.&#xA;Autostarting dunst On most installations, dunst should be able to automatically be started by D-Bus when a notification is sent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Documentation</title>
      <link>https://dunst-project.org/documentation/guides/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dunst-project.org/documentation/guides/</guid>
      <description>Guides Understanding rules Dunst offers some very powerful configuration options in the form of rules. With rules you can change the appearance of notifications, hide some notifications that you don&amp;rsquo;t find useful, change their timeout and much more.&#xA;Example 1: basic rule There are two kinds of rules: filtering rules and modifying rules. These are used for matching a notification and subsequently changing some of it&amp;rsquo;s properties. When no filtering rules are used, all notifications are matched.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://dunst-project.org/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dunst-project.org/faq/</guid>
      <description>Common problems Errors about missing or failing to open a display Depending on the setup dunst was unable to connect to the X server or the wayland compositor in use. In case of X make sure that X is running and that the DISPLAY environment variable is correctly set. For a wayland based setup the WAYLAND_DISPLAY environment variable needs to be set to a valid value.&#xA;If dunst should be automatically started by dbus or via the systemd service, it is important to know that both don&amp;rsquo;t inherit environment variables set by a shell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changelog</title>
      <link>https://dunst-project.org/changelog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dunst-project.org/changelog/</guid>
      <description>1.12.0 &amp;ndash; 2024-11-30 Release Notes Added Export rules via dbus with dunstctl rules [--json] (#1212) Added checks and messages for missing DBUS_SESSION_BUS_ADDRESS (#1389) Add -e/--exit flag to dunstctl is-paused to exit with 1 when paused (#1378) Add color gradients for the progress bar (by providing a list of colors instead of one) (#1370) Use TESTDIR env var as the base for the test program (#1376) Add dunstctl reload to hot reload the configuration (#1350) Add an optional id to dunstctl close (#1351) Print compile-time options in dunst --version (#1336) Changed BREAKING: Implement dynamic height (changes the the height setting, see manual) (#1342) Change the preferred syntax of offset from NxN to (N,N) (#1330) Install the systemd service file in the session.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes</title>
      <link>https://dunst-project.org/release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dunst-project.org/release/</guid>
      <description>Dunst v1.12.0 Changelog There have been many important contributions in the last few months. Some notable changes are: adding hot-reload for the configuration, exporting rules via dunstctl, adding color gradients, removing default hard-coded icons. For detailed information consult the changelog.&#xA;Important notice for all users:&#xA;The behaviour of the setting height has been changed in a breaking way. Before you could specify a single value that would be used as the max height of a notification.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
