<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Dunst</title>
    <link>https://dunst-project.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Dunst</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://dunst-project.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Screenshots</title>
      <link>https://dunst-project.org/screenshots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunst-project.org/screenshots/</guid>
      <description> Config file here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Download</title>
      <link>https://dunst-project.org/download/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunst-project.org/download/</guid>
      <description>The current stable version of Dunst is 1.6.1 released on Feb 21 2021.
Downloads  Source tarball Code repository (Github)  Release Notes For users:
The most important update from the previous version is the addition of the dunstctl command and dunstify utility, a drop-in notify-send replacement (which existed for a while, but wasn&amp;rsquo;t installed by default). The internal keyboard shortcut support in dunst is now considered deprecated and should be replaced by dunstctl calls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changelog</title>
      <link>https://dunst-project.org/changelog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunst-project.org/changelog/</guid>
      <description>1.6.1 - 2021-02-21: Fixed  Incorrect version in Makefile  1.6.0 - 2021-02-21: Added  Wayland support. Dunst now runs natively on wayland. This fixes several bugs with dunst on wayland and allows idle detection. (#781) A progress bar, useful for showing volume or brightness in notifications (#775) A script in contrib for using the progress bar (#791) dunstctl count for showing the number of notifications (#793) Expose environment variables info about the notification to scripts (#802) text_icon_padding for adding padding between the notification icon and text (#810)  Changed  Dunst now installs a system-wide config in /etc/dunst/dunstrc (#798) Move part of the man page to dunst(5) (#799)  Fixed  history_ignore flag broken when using multiple rules (#747) Divide by zero in radius calculation (#750) Monitor setting overriding follow_mode (#755) Incorrect monitor usage when using multiple X11 screens (#762) Emit signal when paused property changes (#766) dunstify can pass empty appname to libnotify (#768) Incorrect handling of &amp;lsquo;do_action, close&amp;rsquo; mouse action (#778)  Removed  DUNST_COMMAND_{PAUSE,RESUME,TOGGLE} (#830)  1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Documentation</title>
      <link>https://dunst-project.org/documentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunst-project.org/documentation/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://dunst-project.org/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunst-project.org/faq/</guid>
      <description>Common problems Errors about missing or failing to open a display Depending on the setup dunst was unable to connect to the X server or the wayland compositor in use. In case of X make sure that X is running and that the DISPLAY environment variable is correctly set. For a wayland based setup the WAYLAND_DISPLAY environment variable needs to be set to a valid value.
If dunst should be automatically started by dbus or via the systemd service, it is important to know that both don&amp;rsquo;t inherit environment variables set by a shell.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
