<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Dunst</title>
    <link>https://dunst-project.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Dunst</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dunst-project.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Screenshots</title>
      <link>https://dunst-project.org/screenshots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunst-project.org/screenshots/</guid>
      <description>.row img { max-width: 100%; height: auto; }  
Config file here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Download</title>
      <link>https://dunst-project.org/download/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunst-project.org/download/</guid>
      <description>The current stable version of Dunst is 1.5.0 released on Jul 23 2020.
Downloads  Source tarball Code repository (Github)  Release Notes For users:
The most important update from the previous version is the addition of the dunstctl command and dunstify utility, a drop-in notify-send replacement (which existed for a while, but wasn&amp;rsquo;t installed by default). The internal keyboard shortcut support in dunst is now considered deprecated and should be replaced by dunstctl calls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changelog</title>
      <link>https://dunst-project.org/changelog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunst-project.org/changelog/</guid>
      <description>1.5.0 - 2020-07-23 Added  min_icon_size option to automatically scale up icons to a desired value (#674) vertical_alignment option to control the text/icon alignment within the notification (#684) Ability to configure multiple actions for each mouse event (#705) dunstctl command line control client (#651) RGBA support for all color strings (#717) Ability to run multiple scripts for each notification ignore_dbusclose setting (#732)  Changed  dunstify notification client is now installed by default (#701) Keyboard follow mode falls back to the monitor with the mouse if no window has keyboard focus (#708)  Fixed  Overflow when setting a &amp;gt;=40 minute timeout (#646) Unset configuration options not falling back to default values (#649) Crash when $HOME environment variable is unset (#693) Lack of antialiasing with round corners enabled (#713)  1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Documentation</title>
      <link>https://dunst-project.org/documentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunst-project.org/documentation/</guid>
      <description>NAME SYNOPSIS DESCRIPTION COMMAND LINE OPTIONS CONFIGURATION  Command line Global section Shortcut section DEPRECATED SEE DUNSTCTL Urgency sections   DUNSTCTL HISTORY RULES  SCRIPTING   COLORS  NOTIFY-SEND   ACTIONS TIME FORMAT MISCELLANEOUS FILES AUTHORS REPORTING BUGS COPYRIGHT SEE ALSO  NAME dunst - A customizable and lightweight notification-daemon
SYNOPSIS dunst [-conf file] [-font font] [-geometry geom] [-format fmt] [-follow mode] [-monitor n] [-history_length n] ...</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://dunst-project.org/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunst-project.org/faq/</guid>
      <description>Common problems Cannot open display Dunst was unable to connect to the X server. Make sure that X is running and that the DISPLAY environment variable is correctly set.
If you&amp;rsquo;re using the systemd service, that might mean that dbus isn&amp;rsquo;t setting the right variables, see issue #347 for more details.
Cannot connect to DBus Dunst cannot connect to your session bus at all. The session bus might not even exist.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>