<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Dunst</title>
    <link>https://dunst-project.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Dunst</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://dunst-project.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Screenshots</title>
      <link>https://dunst-project.org/screenshots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunst-project.org/screenshots/</guid>
      <description>.row img { max-width: 100%; height: auto; }  
Config file here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Download</title>
      <link>https://dunst-project.org/download/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunst-project.org/download/</guid>
      <description>The current stable version of Dunst is 1.7.3 released on Dec 8 2021.
Downloads  Source tarball Code repository (Github)  Release Notes for v1.7.0 This release was long overdue. There have been a lot of changes in the mean time. For a full list of changes, see the changelog.
For users:
The wayland support of v1.6.0 was already pretty good, but this release added fullscreen detection and improved the stability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Documentation</title>
      <link>https://dunst-project.org/documentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunst-project.org/documentation/</guid>
      <description>dunst - configuration file   NAME DESCRIPTION  Global section Urgency sections   DUNSTCTL HISTORY WAYLAND RULES  SCRIPTING   COLORS  NOTIFY-SEND   ACTIONS TIME FORMAT MISCELLANEOUS AUTHORS REPORTING BUGS COPYRIGHT SEE ALSO  NAME dunst - configuration file
DESCRIPTION The configuration is divided into sections in an ini-like format. Every section start with the section&amp;#39;s name in square brackets. After that is a list of key-value pairs that specify the settings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Documentation</title>
      <link>https://dunst-project.org/documentation_header/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunst-project.org/documentation_header/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://dunst-project.org/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunst-project.org/faq/</guid>
      <description>Common problems Errors about missing or failing to open a display Depending on the setup dunst was unable to connect to the X server or the wayland compositor in use. In case of X make sure that X is running and that the DISPLAY environment variable is correctly set. For a wayland based setup the WAYLAND_DISPLAY environment variable needs to be set to a valid value.
If dunst should be automatically started by dbus or via the systemd service, it is important to know that both don&amp;rsquo;t inherit environment variables set by a shell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://dunst-project.org/changelog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunst-project.org/changelog/</guid>
      <description>Dunst changelog 1.7.3 &amp;ndash; 2021-12-08 Added Changed  follow is now none again by default. This was the case before v1.7.0 as well. (#990).  Fixed  dunstctl action is now working again. Segfault in experimental icon lookup when an inherited theme doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist. icon_position = off not being respected (#996).  1.7.2 &amp;ndash; 2021-11-30 Added  Experimental recursive icon lookup. This is not enabled by default and can be enabled by setting enable_recursive_icon_lookup=true.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
