<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Dunst</title>
    <link>https://dunst-project.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Dunst</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dunst-project.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Screenshots</title>
      <link>https://dunst-project.org/screenshots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunst-project.org/screenshots/</guid>
      <description>.row img { max-width: 100%; height: auto; }  
Config file here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Download</title>
      <link>https://dunst-project.org/download/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunst-project.org/download/</guid>
      <description>The current stable version of Dunst is 1.3.0 released on Jan 5 2018.
Downloads  Source tarball Code repository (Github)  Release Notes Version 1.3 is supposed to be fully backwards compatible with 1.2.
For users:
 Behavioural changes
Dunst respects the timeout with millisecond accuracy now. Notifications with a one second timeout are not shown up to three seconds. Additionally you can specify timeout values in milliseconds, seconds, minutes, hours or days using the ms, s, h, or d suffix in the config value respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changelog</title>
      <link>https://dunst-project.org/changelog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunst-project.org/changelog/</guid>
      <description>1.3.0 - 2018-01-05 Added  ellipsize option to control how long lines should be ellipsized when word_wrap is set to false (#374) A beginning tilde of a path is now expanded to the home of the current user (#351) The image-path hint is now respected, as GApplications send their icon only via this link (#447) The (legacy) image_data hint is now respected (#353) If dunst can&amp;rsquo;t acquire the DBus name, dunst prints the PID of the process holding the name (#458 #460) Increased accuracy of timeouts by using microseconds internally (#379 #291) Support for specifying timeout values in milliseconds, minutes, hours, or days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://dunst-project.org/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dunst-project.org/faq/</guid>
      <description>Common problems Cannot open display Dunst was unable to connect to the X server. Make sure that X is running and that the DISPLAY environment variable is correctly set.
If you&amp;rsquo;re using the systemd service, that might mean that dbus isn&amp;rsquo;t setting the right variables, see issue #347 for more details.
Cannot connect to DBus Dunst cannot connect to you session bus at all. The session bus might not even exist.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>